Admittedly, I haven't had my head in the
US real estate market very much in the
last couple years. Now that I'm back, I
have seen that things have gone downhill
a whole lot. Talked to all my buddies in
investing here at Augusta, and they said
interest rates up, price of everything
up, days on market up, real estate sales
down, rentals longer on market, and
everything else is kind of going rough
for everybody. This is a pretty tough
time, and I don't know what caused it,
and I don't know how to fix it, but I
know that we're all in this together.
We're all just busting our ass trying to
get our head above water. Times like
this, you kind of think about all the
people in the Bible. Did God save Noah?
Noah believed God, built a boat at a
time when it had not rained on Earth,
and it took him like 40 years. Do you
think Noah was made fun of? Yes. Do you
think Noah was criticized? Yes. But Noah
just kept building his little boat
because he knew that it was going to
come a time when he would need it.
That's the mode I'm in right now, Noah
mode. Out here fixing things as fast as
I can, and just putting one foot in
front of the other. To my real estate
people, best of luck. I'm out here
swinging with you. Working with this
ladder and the lovely Alex. Alex, how
are things going?
>> It's good.
>> Yeah.
>> It's great. We're going to get through
it. Noah mode.